this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to become the
next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture the
unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
in search of a ship coding craftsman to help them reach fishman island the straw hat crew landed on
the sabaody archipelago this mission led them to rayleigh a craftsman and former vice captain of
the roger pirates on the run from the navy luffy and the crew decided to lay low while rayleigh modified
the sunny for underwater travel then suddenly they were ambushed by the warlord of the sea bartholomew kuma
three sword style all right now gum gum about some diable
but zorro wondered if this was the real kuma
well he's plenty
strong as is and what's worse the real one might be after us as well
meanwhile several of the supernovas squared off against admiral kizaru an assassin sent by navy
headquarters
this is barcelino
what the heck uncle you do have a baby transponder snail why didn't you contact me
huh oh is that you sent tomorrow don't give me that is that you business where are you what are you
doing i tried contacting you before but i couldn't get a hold of you
it's fine forget it it's time we get to work now it seems the culprits have split up
straw hat luffy captain eustace kid and trafalgar law which one do we start with huh split up in that case well
this bastard wants us dead but if he's not bartholomew kuma who the hell is he either way we don't have
time for this crap if we don't get out of here we're gonna be even worse off than we are now
an even stronger enemy appears the battle-axe carrying sentamaru
so
listen trafalgar you're in my damn way now get out of here
i've got this i'm taking him down you got it backwards you're in my way now run along
room
nothing but laser beams i expected more from a warlord of the sea there they are
trafalgar law captain of the heart pirates and eustace kid captain of the kid pirates don't let
him escape yes sir crap we got a whole mess of marines coming up on us we're boxed in if this
situation could get any worse i don't know how quick come with me peppo we're busting through hey you're
the new guy you can't just go giving me orders we follow protocol
that bastard he went and took all the fun for himself
repel
something's wrong you can't be bartholomew kuma that guy ain't no warlord
uh
dan we can hardly lay a finger on him
already
that dude
even
um
is
could
No, Ben!
Don't get on me, Daddy!
Chopper!
Let's drop hammer!
Cranky Boxing!
Spider-neck!
Hey, you don't need to punch so hard!
The lasers are enough!
Good luck dodging this!
I dare say you're in for it.
Here it comes, Swallow Bandero!
Wait...
I'm stuck!
That was not my plan!
Hold on!
No!
Please do!
Let's be reasonable about this!
I'd rather you not kill me right now!
Although, you know, I am already dead, but...
I feel like that's beside the plane!
This special attack at the summit!
Now's our chance!
Run like hell!
I feel like I can't pick you enough!
Huh?
Hey, check it out!
He's down!
What the?
Wait, so explosives work on him all of a sudden?
They sank one of them into his mouth.
It must have shorted out something inside of him.
His body may be hard as steel, but his skin still bleeds.
He's just like me.
He's got a normal old human body.
It's been modified, and it's stopped.
It's been modified.
It's done!
You know, we've proved to be able to getğl Private Redman to play!
Thank you!
It is!
Erfahrung!
Pronounce this guy's semblance to buке!
Let's beat Eminem.
That's he doesn't bite!
Come on!
Then just...
It's just the same!
Not happened!
All the objects that make yourdert政治 position!!
You mean, you only work there, right?
You could walk the street at the entrance, however.
They sank one of them into his mouth.
It must have shorted out something inside of him.
His body may be hard if steel, but his skin still bleeds.
He's just like me.
He's got a normal old human body.
It's been modified, and stuck full of weapons.
Holy crap!
In shock.
Nice one! Who needs to fight when we can just make him blow himself up?
We should have thought of this before!
Hey, you might want to sit somewhere else.
That spot is under a storm warning.
From the dark clouds to my climb attack, Thunderbolt Tensile!
So, did it work or not?
That attack didn't slow him down at all! The only thing it did is piss him off!
What's he aiming at? He's firing everywhere!
He looks desperate to me!
Desperate? He's lost his damn mind!
He's the same as admitting you've lost the fight!
Desperation's the same as admitting you've lost the fight!
Hey! Knock his ass over here!
Gotta have a piece of the action, huh?
Diable Shamba!
Flam-bay-shot!
Nice! We're finally starting to wear him down!
Demon Aura!
Nine sword style!
Ashura!
What is my fishing part?
So many Zoros!
Nine lightning strikes!
Turn gear!
Here, boom!
Whippy, smash him!
Just one last push!
Go, boom!
Moopy, go!
You lose!
Ah!
I don't need any of seu money!
Yaaayin!
olmay slight
the
The
I'm shrinking!
That do it? Is he done?
Seems like it. About time.
Geez, he looks fine. Creepy.
If he's fine, then we are screwed. I'm too tired to move anymore.
You know, maybe we should have run instead of fighting.
No. It's best to take them on as they come, one at a time.
We're being chased. We can't get cornered.
True. But still, he wasn't Kuma. Who was he?
We know he's a cyborg, so he must have been a person at some point.
But, if this guy isn't the real Bartholomew Kuma, then why the heck does he look just like him?
Maybe the guy's got a twin? If not, they must have modified the crap out of him to make him look the same.
Can't imagine why, though. He couldn't have been created from scratch. You can't do that with a living person.
PX4? Huh.
We need to get some rest. I was up for a fight, but that guy was way too much for me. I'm exhausted.
A break would be nice. But we've got to find a place to hide first. If they find us now, there's no way we can fight them off.
Yeah, I know. But let's just sit here for a few minutes.
You guys got some real nerve. Look what you've done!
What the? Another enemy? Where is he?
There he is! Up there!
Who are you?
I'm disgusted. You're an utter disgrace, PX4. The Navy's not made of money. Building just one of you pacifistas costs as much as an entire warship.
Seriously. You know how this is gonna look in my report to that lousy Vegapunk?
He's got another wine line with him!
Are you kidding me? Is that the real one?
Does it really matter if it's the real one or not? We've already gotten a taste of how strong the fakes are.
We can't take another fight, not with him.
Wait. Pacifista?
Yeah, that's what he called him. He didn't seem like much of a pacifist, though. So, you think that's his name or something?
Alright, Axe Boy. Just who the hell are ya?
I've got an identity outside of my axe, you know. And there's no point in asking questions. I have no reason to answer you. I am the most well-guarded and tight-lipped man alive. Nobody can break down my impenetrable defenses.
Oh, come on. You could at least tell us your name.
Did you hear a single thing I just told you? My lips are sealed. Trust me. There's not one person more secretive than me. Sentomaru.
Gotcha. So you're Sentomaru.
Uh... To be clear, I wanted you to know that. That's why I told you. And not because you wanted to know, okay?
PX1, let's get started.
Still no paw bubbles. This guy shoots beams from his hands, too. It's starting to look like they've got a whole army of these guys. What is this crowd?
I'm more concerned with staying alive. The mystery can wait. We're too worn down. There's just no way we can make it through another fight when we haven't even met the Admiral.
Yeah. We can't win. Let's run. But not all together. We need to split up.
Sounds good to me! Run!
We're the toughest. We'll each lead our own group.
Right. Are you gonna be okay on your own? Hey, shut up!
Wait up, Navi! We should stick together! I'll protect you no matter what, even if it means sacrificing my life!
Fine! Thanks! Now run! Faster!
If you're really willing to sacrifice yourself, why don't you hang back and act as a decoy?
It's a ladies-only offer, idiot. You can take care of your own damn self, Panty Man.
Koro! Don't let me die! Protect me with all your mind, okay?
Stop! I'm already in enough pain as it is!
Fret not, my friend. I'll proudly supply the strength you currently lack. I can only imagine how much healing you've left to do.
I happened to witness your act of selfless bravery on Thriller Bark when you offered your own life in place of Luffy's.
All right. Thanks.
Up there! Head that way!
Got it!
No more laser phase!
Hey! Guys! Meet back on the Sonia 3D!
They're splitting into groups! Go after them, PX1!
Make sure you don't let him out of Grove 12!
We don't need that headache!
Special attack!
Super Smokestar!
Now's our chance! Run for us!
You really are quite dependable!
He took out the bridge!
Here he comes!
No! Why the apparatus?
Look, I don't know, but will you quit pushing me?
He's over there! Are you guys okay?
I'd worry about myself if I were you!
I've got no grudge against you pirates, but a job is a job!
Now, come, go!
Got me!
Point shot!
What the?
What? How do you even do that?
Your offensive skills are impressive, but they're useless against my defense!
Has she got a no point job?
Luffy! Oh boy! This guy is strong!
Just so you know, I don't even have Devil Fruit powers!
That makes it worse! Man, this is weird!
Thanks for the warning! I thought you were supposed to be protecting me, you jerk!
Get down!
Moro!
Who? Who are you? What are you? Whatever! Just get the hell away from Zoro!
Oh no, no, Zoro! He got hit by one of those laser beams!
Hang in there, buddy! Come on!
It's about time you got here! Took you long enough, Uncle Kizaru!
Kizaru?
Hey, Usopp! Be careful! That man's a Navy Admiral!
An Admiral! Uh-oh!
Your time is up, Pirate Hunter Zoro.
Last I checked, you had 120 million bounty, so this is not what I was expecting.
Your reputation as a swordsman is known far and wide.
But one hit and you're down? That's a real shame, ain't it?
You must be pretty worn out, hmm?
Damn! The Admiral found us!
Well, you'll have plenty of time to rest up now.
Zoro!
A warlord? That weirdo with a big axe and now an Admiral too?
I know you're having a real tough time, but what can I say? I'm good at my job.
I hate to admit it, but these guys are too strong for us! Everyone run for it! Just don't die!
On the next One Piece! Admiral Kizaru's fierce assault! The Straw Hats face certain death! I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Time!